// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  //   {
  //   numb: 1,
  //   question: "What does HTML stand for?",
  //   answer: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
  //   options: [
  //     "Hyper Text Preprocessor",
  //     "Hyper Text Markup Language",
  //     "Hyper Text Multiple Language",
  //     "Hyper Tool Multi Language"
  //   ]
  // },
  //   {
  //   numb: 2,
  //   question: "What does CSS stand for?",
  //   answer: "Cascading Style Sheet",
  //   options: [
  //     "Common Style Sheet",
  //     "Colorful Style Sheet",
  //     "Computer Style Sheet",
  //     "Cascading Style Sheet"
  //   ]
  // },
  //   {
  //   numb: 3,
  //   question: "What does PHP stand for?",
  //   answer: "Hypertext Preprocessor",
  //   options: [
  //     "Hypertext Preprocessor",
  //     "Hypertext Programming",
  //     "Hypertext Preprogramming",
  //     "Hometext Preprocessor"
  //   ]
  // },
  //   {
  //   numb: 4,
  //   question: "What does SQL stand for?",
  //   answer: "Structured Query Language",
  //   options: [
  //     "Stylish Question Language",
  //     "Stylesheet Query Language",
  //     "Statement Question Language",
  //     "Structured Query Language"
  //   ]
  // },
  //   {
  //   numb: 5,
  //   question: "What does XML stand for?",
  //   answer: "eXtensible Markup Language",
  //   options: [
  //     "eXtensible Markup Language",
  //     "eXecutable Multiple Language",
  //     "eXTra Multi-Program Language",
  //     "eXamine Multiple Language"
  //   ]
  // },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which process is most suitable for converting 'Sulphide ore' into 'Oxides' ?",
    answer: "Roasting",
    options: [
      "Roasting",
      "Calcination",
      "Electrolysis",
      "Heating"
    ]
  },
  

  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is/are NOBLE GAS ?",
    answer: "Both (1) & (2)",
    options: [
      "Neon",
      "Argon",
      "Both (1) & (2)",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Number of Electrons in outermost cell of Sodium is:",
    answer: "1",
    options: [
      "1",
      "2",
      "3",
      "-1"
    ]
  },



  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "HCL and Nitric Acid are mixed in AQUA REGIA in ratio:",
    answer: "3:1",
    options: [
      "4:1",
      "2:1",
      "5:1",
      "3:1"
    ]
  },



  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which part of nerve cell contain nucleus :",
    answer: "Cyton",
    options: [
      "Axon",
      "Cyton",
      "Dendrite",
      "Nerve ending"
    ]
  },




  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "According to Quantum Theory , LIGHT is :",
    answer: "None of these",
    options: [
      "Particle",
      "Wave",
      "both 1 and 2",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },


  {
    numb: 7,
    question: " CHO  represents the Functional Group :",
    answer: "Aldehydes",
    options: [
      "Alcohol",
      "Aldehydes",
      "Ester",
      "Carboxylic acid"
    ]
  },



{
  numb: 8,
  question: "pH of Pure Blood and Water is :",
  answer: "7.4",
  options: [
    "7.4",
    "6.4",
    "7.9",
    "6.9"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 9,
  question: "The self linking property is maximum in :",
  answer: "Carbon",
  options: [
    "Carbon",
    "Silicon",
    "Phosphorus",
    "Sulphur"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 10,
  question: "How many pairs of cranial nerve is present in human?",
  answer: "12",
  options: [
    "10",
    "12",
    "14",
    "16"
  ]
},


{
  numb: 11,
  question: "How  many Covalent Bonds present in PENTANE ?",
  answer: "16",
  options: [
    "10",
    "12",
    "15",
    "16"
  ]
},


{
  numb: 12,
  question: "The Law of Reflection holds for :",
  answer: "Any highly polished surface irrespective of their shape",
  options: [
    "Plane Mirror only",
    "Any highly polished surface irrespective of their shape",
    "Spherical Mirror only",
    "parabolic mirror only"
  ]
},


{
 numb: 13,
  question: "The device that identiifes the Presence of current in circuit is:",
  answer: "Galvanometer",
  options: [
    "Ammeter",
    "Voltmeter",
    "Galvanometer",
    "all of these"
  ]
},

{
  numb: 14,
   question: "Spore Formation occurs in :",
   answer: "Rizhopus",
   options: [
     "Plasmodium",
     "Planaria",
     "Leishmania",
     "Rizhopus"
   ]
 },

 {
  numb: 15,
   question: "A piece of material that has both attractive and directive properties is called :",
   answer: "Magnet",
   options: [
     "Iron fillings",
     "Magnet",
     "Coil(inductor)",
     "Resistor"
   ]
 },

 {
  numb: 16,
   question: "What is the resistance of ideal VOLTMETER ?",
   answer: "Infinite",
   options: [
     "0",
     "Infinite",
     "Depend on Current and Voltage",
     "Can't be known"
   ]
 },

 {
  numb: 17,
   question: "Name the physical quantity whose unit is J/C.",
   answer: "Electric potential",
   options: [
     "Work",
     "Electric charge",
     "Electric potential",
     "Electric Power"
   ]
 },


 {
  numb: 18,
   question: "How is the ammeter connected in the circuit?",
   answer: "in Series",
   options: [
     "in Parallel",
     "in Series",
     "none of these",
     "Anyway"
   ]
 },


 {
  numb: 19,
   question: "Photosynthesis is a :",
   answer: "Endothermic reaction",
   options: [
     "Displacement reaction",
     "Coombustion reaction",
     "Exothermic reaction",
     "Endothermic reaction"
   ]
 },

 {
  numb: 20,
   question: "Which of the following is an antioxidant ?",
   answer: "Both 2 and 3",
   options: [
     "Nitrogen",
     "Butylated Hydroxy Anisole (BHA)",
     "Butylated Hydroxy Toluene (BHT)",
     "Both 2 and 3"
   ]
 },

 {
  numb: 21,
   question: "The black opening between the Aqueous humour and lens is called :",
   answer: "Pupil",
   options: [
     "Pupil",
     "Iris",
     "Cornea",
     "retina"
   ]
 },


 {
  numb: 22,
   question: "Which of the following are chiefly digested in Stomach?",
   answer: "Protein",
   options: [
     "Lipid",
     "Fat",
     "Protein",
     "Carbohydrate"
   ]
 },

//  {
//   numb: 21,
//    question: "",
//    answer: "",
//    options: [
//      "",
//      "",
//      "",
//      ""
//    ]
//  },



//  {
//   numb: 21,
//    question: "",
//    answer: "",
//    options: [
//      "",
//      "",
//      "",
//      ""
//    ]
//  },


//  {
//   numb: 21,
//    question: "",
//    answer: "",
//    options: [
//      "",
//      "",
//      "",
//      ""
//    ]
//  },


//  {
//   numb: 21,
//    question: "",
//    answer: "",
//    options: [
//      "",
//      "",
//      "",
//      ""
//    ]
//  },


//  {
//   numb: 21,
//    question: "",
//    answer: "",
//    options: [
//      "",
//      "",
//      "",
//      ""
//    ]
//  },


//  {
//   numb: 21,
//    question: "",
//    answer: "",
//    options: [
//      "",
//      "",
//      "",
//      ""
//    ]
//  },


//  {
//   numb: 21,
//    question: "",
//    answer: "",
//    options: [
//      "",
//      "",
//      "",
//      ""
//    ]
//  },


//  {
//   numb: 21,
//    question: "",
//    answer: "",
//    options: [
//      "",
//      "",
//      "",
//      ""
//    ]
//  },


//  {
//   numb: 21,
//    question: "",
//    answer: "",
//    options: [
//      "",
//      "",
//      "",
//      ""
//    ]
//  },


//  {
//   numb: 21,
//    question: "",
//    answer: "",
//    options: [
//      "",
//      "",
//      "",
//      ""
//    ]
//  },

//  {
//   numb: 21,
//    question: "",
//    answer: "",
//    options: [
//      "",
//      "",
//      "",
//      ""
//    ]
//  },


//  {
//   numb: 21,
//    question: "",
//    answer: "",
//    options: [
//      "",
//      "",
//      "",
//      ""
//    ]
//  },


];